<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Descriptions (MAX CHARACTERS = 300) -->
    <!-- Historical Sites -->
    <string name="meiji_jingu_description">Meiji Shrine, located in Shibuya,
        Tokyo, is the Shinto shrine that is dedicated to the deified spirits of Emperor Meiji and his wife, Empress Shōken.
        The shrine does not contain the emperor\'s grave, which is located at Fushimi-momoyama, south of Kyoto.
        If you are lucky enough you may encounter a traditional wedding happening in the shrine.</string>
    <string name="nezu_shrine_description">Nezu Shrine is a Shinto shrine located in Tokyo, Japan. Established in 1705,
        it is one of the oldest places of worship in the city,
        and several of the buildings on the shrine grounds have been designated as Important Cultural Property.</string>
    <string name="asakusa_description">Asakusa is famous for the Sensō-ji, a Buddhist temple
        dedicated to the bodhisattva Kannon, and the Nakamise street.
        There are several other temples in Asakusa, as well as various festivals, such as the Sanja Matsuri
        and the fireworks in summer. Also there are several traditional restaurants surrounding the temple</string>
    <string name="camii_description">Tokyo Mosque, Tōkyō-jāmii also known as Tokyo Camii,
        is a mosque with an adjoining Turkish culture center located.
        Close from Yoyogi-uehara station. It is known as one of the most beautiful mosques in all
        of Asia, being the largest mosque in Japan. </string>
    <string name="akasaka_description">Akasaka Palace, or the State Guest House, is one
        of the two state guest houses of the Government of Japan.
        The other state guesthouse is the Kyoto State Guest House. The palace was originally
        built as the Imperial Palace for the Crown Prince in 1909.</string>
    <string name="tokyo_skytree_description">Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting and observation
        tower. It became the tallest structure in Japan reaching
        its full height of 634 meters in 2011,
        making it the tallest tower in the world, and the second after the construction of Burj Khalifa.</string>
    <string name="tokyo_tower_description">Built in 1958 reaching 332.9 meters, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan.
        The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that
        is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.</string>
    <string name="ginza_description">One of the city’s top shopping districts, Ginza is packed with upmarket boutiques and ritzy cocktail and sushi bars.
        Fine jewelry is sold in the 1930s Wako Honkan department store.
        Traditional dance and drama is staged at the Kabuki theater. This is the place to buy all your souvenirs.</string>
    <string name="tokyo_station_description">The main station on the western side
        of the station is brick-built, surviving from the time when the station opened in 1914.
        The building was designed by architect Tatsuno Kingo, as a restrained celebration of victory in the Russo-Japanese War.</string>

    <!-- Museums -->
    <string name="edo_tokyo_description">The museum opened in March 1993 to preserve Edo\'s cultural heritage,
        and features city models of Edo and Tokyo between 1590 and 1964.
        It was the first museum built dedicated to the history of Tokyo. One of the best historical Museums in Japan.
        It includes a partial replica of the original wooden nihonbashi (which was destroyed during the bombings of 1945.)</string>
    <string name="samurai_museum_description">It\'s a strong tourist activity featuring costumes that can be worn by visitors, regular sword battles and more.
        That being said, it offers a small peek into what being a samurai was, their story, and their believes.</string>
    <string name="nature_science_description">Opened in 1871, offers a wide variety of natural history exhibitions and interactive scientific experiences.
    Highly recommendable if you are traveling with children or if you are a science geek.</string>
    <string name="tokyo_national_description">It is one of the four museums operated by
        the National Institutes for Cultural Heritage, is considered the oldest national museum in Japan,
        is the largest art museum in Japan, and is one of the largest art museums in the world. For
        this reason we highly advise you to go there early in the morning.</string>
    <string name="ghibli_description">Animation and art museum of Studio Ghibli, one of Japan\'s most famous animation studios.
        They have produced many feature length films with worldwide distribution such as My Neighbor Totoro,
        Princess Mononoke, Spirited Away and many others. You must reserve the entrance
        a month before your planned visit.</string>
    <string name="western_art_description">The National Museum of Western Art is the premier public art gallery in Japan
        specializing in art from the Western tradition.
        Exhibits works from the Renaissance to the early 20th century, many having been acquired since the museum\'s opening.</string>
    <string name="teamLab_description">teamLab Planets is a museum where you walk through water.
        It consists of four vast exhibition spaces containing seven indoor “Body Immersive” artworks,
        plus one outdoor piece at the entrance for a total of eight works created by teamLab.</string>

    <!-- Parks -->
    <string name="yoyogi_description">One of Tokyo\'s largest city parks, featuring wide lawns, ponds and forested areas.
        It is a great place for jogging, picnicking and other outdoor activities.
        Known for its ginko tree forest, which turns intensely golden in autumn.</string>
    <string name="shiba_park_description">Shiba Park is Japan\'s oldest public park, being the first to be officially designated as a park in 1873,
        only five years after the beginning of Japan\'s modernization. Parts of the present day park were once the Edo-period Okubo clan garden.</string>
    <string name="ueno_park_description">The park grounds were originally part of Kaneiji Temple, which used to be one of the city\'s
        largest and wealthiest temples and a family temple of the ruling Tokugawa clan during the Edo Period.</string>
    <string name="nature_study_description">The Institute for Nature Study is a nature reserve in the heart of Tokyo.
        The sights and sounds of the city are left behind when you enter the park.
        Wild, natural and quiet even though the grounds are located near the Yamanote Line.</string>
    <string name="shinjuku_gyoen_description">One of Tokyo\'s largest and most popular parks. Located just a short walk from Shinjuku Station, the paid park\'s
        spacious lawns, meandering walking paths and tranquil scenery provide a relaxing escape from the busy urban center around it. </string>
    <string name="imperial_garden_description">Part of the inner palace area and open to the public. Former site of Edo Castle\'s innermost circles of defense,
        the honmaru and ninomaru.
        None of the main buildings remain today, but the moats, walls, entrance gates and several guardhouses still exist.</string>
    <string name="rikyu_garden_description">Features seawater ponds which change level with the tides,
        and a teahouse on an island where visitors can rest and enjoy the scenery.
        The traditionally styled garden stands in stark contrast to the skyscrapers of the adjacent Shiodome district.</string>
    <string name="mount_takao_description">Takaosan has been a center of mountain worship for more than 1000 years. Yakuoin, an attractive temple,
        stands along the trail near the mountain\'s summit, and many visitors stop there to pray to Shinto-Buddhist mountain gods (tengu) for good fortune.</string>
    <string name="nokogiri_mountain_description">Spread out along the slopes of the mountain is Nihonji Temple, a Buddhist temple, which was commissioned about 1300 years ago,
        making it one of the oldest places of worship in the Kanto Region. Up the mountain are 1500 statues of Buddhist disciples.</string>

    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="ise_sueyoshi_description">Genre: Sashimi. \nIdeal for enjoying the four seasons of Japan on a plate.
        Displays a rich experience with and deep understanding of the ingredients,
        conveying not only the passing seasons but also the scenery and traditional flavors of Japan.</string>
    <string name="miyazono_description">Genre: Sushi. \nThere are only nine seats in this elegant restaurant, so book in advance or turn up late – but not too late,
        because Miyazono doesn’t serve food to customers who arrive after 1am. He’s got to sleep some time.</string>
    <string name="kaneko_description">Genre: Tempura. \nHow long would you wait for a good bowl of
        topped rice? An hour? More? We waited an hour and half on a Monday lunchtime in the queue that snaked outside this humble tendon specialist.
        Ask for the large portion if you’re hungry. </string>
    <string name="izumoya_description">Genre: Unagi. \nAn incongruous sight amongst the glass-and-steel high-rises of Nihonbashi,
        the traditional two-storey building housing unagi specialist Izumoya seems to have somehow been shielded from the modern world.</string>
    <string name="honmura_description">Genre: Soba. \nThe spacious, light interior and contemporary décor has helped draw a mix of locals and tourists
        who are determined to sit down and appreciate their soba at an appropriately slow pace.</string>
    <string name="kanda_description">Genre: Soba. \nMatsuya counts among Tokyo\'s most venerable noodle joints – it\'s been in business since 1884,
        and the current, gorgeously preserved building dates back to 1924. </string>
    <string name="oniyanma_description">Genre: Udon. \nOutside Gotanda station, this rough-and-ready joint serves up bowls
        from as low as ¥300, and attracts queues every single day at lunchtime.
        The tempura here is always freshly fried, so make sure to order some to go with your noodles.</string>
    <string name="land_description">Genre: Curry. \nGenre: curry. Land is a small Meguro restaurant with a big ambition –
        to reinvent the Japanese curry. Naito’s complex, aromatic sauce,
        made with chicken stock, onion, garlic and a 15-spice mix, performs gymnastics on the tongue.</string>
    <string name="mouyan_description">Genre: Curry. \nAt Mouyan you can enjoy curry prepared with the utmost care.
        Onions, carrots, tomatoes, apples and bananas are broiled for two weeks in order to prepare the roux that\'s
        added to the stock and cooked for two days to get on your dish.</string>
    <string name="tonkyu_description">Genre: Tonkatsu. \nTakadanobaba
        is home to several tonkatsu restaurants boasting citywide popularity. These regularly attract lengthy queues of
        carnivores who don\'t mind waiting for what could be hours to bite into an extra-juicy piece of meat.</string>
    <string name="karubiano_description">Genre: Yakiniku. \nAt Karubiano in Shinbashi it’s all about the careful selection of Japanese beef.
        The thin strips are cooked over a charcoal grill at the ten-seat counter, browning in less than a minute.</string>

</resources>